(Bernadette:)I know. I'm sorry.
(Bernadette:)- I got scared.
- If you're gonna love me...
(Howard:)...you're gonna have
to love the whole package.
(Howard:)The tenderhearted poet
and the crazy daredevil.
(Amy:)- I know.
- Don't say it if you're not gonna mean it.
(Howard:)I'm not just gonna stop
with the space station.
(Howard:)Yeah, I want to go to the moon,
I want to go to Mars.
(Howard:)I want to take a one-man sub
to the Iowest depths of the ocean.
(Bernadette:)Really? You got seasick
on Pirates of the Caribbean.
Well, those big kids were rocking it, heh.
(Bernadette:)I just did what I did
because I love you so much...
(Bernadette:)...and the thought of losing you
is more than I can handle.
- Really?
- You're my soul mate.
(Bernadette:)- This is where you kiss me.
- Right, right, heh.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Make up all you want!
Your tokus is not leaving this planet!